applicationData = {
	"name": "KBC Quizzo",
	"repository": "https://hind-sagar-biswas/kbcQuizzo/",
	"mainLanguage": "JavaScript",
	"allLanguage": [
		"JavaScript",
		"JSON",
		"HTML",
		"CSS"
	],
	"frameworks": null,
	"authorData": {
		"name": "Hind Sagar Biswas",
		"email": "hindsbhk@gmail.com",
		"website": "hindbiswas.000webhostapp.com",
		"github": "https://github.com/hind-sagar-biswas/"
	},
	"versionData" : {
		"stable": {
			"name": "notReleased",
			"tag": "notReleased"
		},
		"preRelease": {
			"name": "Beta 4",
			"tag": "v1.0.8"
		}
	},
	"license": {
		"name": "GNU AGPLv3",
		"type": "strong copyleft"
	}
}
data = [
		{
			"question" : "What is the name of the largest star of the world ever discovered by human?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "UY Scuti",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"KW Sagitarii",
				"V354 Cephei",
				"Sun"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "When the moon appears darkened as it passes into the earth's shadow?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Lunar Eclipse",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Moon Eclipse",
				"Apocalyps",
				"Solar Eclipse"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What is the most precious material of the world?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Antimatter",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Diamond",
				"Californium",
				"Dark-matter"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "Which planet is called the sister of earth?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "astronomy",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Venus",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Mars",
				"Saturn",
				"Jupiter"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "Which is the largest animal ever lived on earth?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Blue Whale",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Argentinosorus",
				"Titanoboa"
				"Megalodon"
			]
		
		},
		{
			"question" : "Which is the slowest animal?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Sloth",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Snail",
				"Lobster",
				"Tortoise"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What is the highest-grossing film of all time without taking inflation into account?",
			"category" : "entertainment",
			"subCategory" : "movies",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Avengers: Endgame",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Titanic",
				"Avatar",
				"Star Wars: The Force Awakens"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What was the first feature-length animated film ever released?",
			"category" : "entertainment",
			"subCategory" : "animations",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Pinocchio",
				"Fantasia",
				"Dumbo"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What team has the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
			"category" : "entertainment",
			"subCategory" : "sports",
			"difficulty" : "hard",
			"answer" : "Los Angeles Lakers",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Chicago Bulls",
				"Golden State Warriors",
				"Phoenix Suns"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What is the largest country in the world?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "geography",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Russia",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"India",
				"USA",
				"Canada"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "A doctor with a PhD is a doctor of what?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "generalScience",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "Philosophy",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Psychology",
				"Phrenology",
				"Physical Therapy"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "Which ocean borders the west coast of the United States?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "geography",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "Pacific",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Indian",
				"Arctic",
				"Atlantic"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "According to legend, what item is most effective against werewolves?",
			"category" : "mythsAndLegends",
			"subCategory" : "urbanLegends",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Silver",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Gold",
				"Copper",
				"Lead"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "How many elements are there in a periodic table?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chemistry",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "118",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"121",
				"120",
				"119"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What's called the process of producing Food in Plants?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "biology",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Photosynthesis",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Phosphorylation",
				"Pollination",
				"Osmosis"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "How many phenomenons of light occurs when light is sent from one medium to another?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "physics",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "3",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"2",
				"4",
				"5"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What type of wave is light?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "physics",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Electromagnetic",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Mechanical",
				"Gravitational",
				"Light is not a wave"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "How many types of hydrocarbon are there?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chemistry",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "2",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"3",
				"4",
				"5"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "Which one is an impossible hydrocarbon?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chemistry",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "Methene",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Methane",
				"Ethane",
				"Ethene"
			]
		}
	]
